我们就快将我们的应用
We're almost at the point where we are going to
提交收录到Windows Store中了
submit our application for ingestion to the Windows Store.
但是，在那之前
However, before we get to that,
让你们看一下本宝宝是怎么解决
let me just show you what I did to resolve
上节课遗留的问题的
the issue that we left in the previous lesson.
本宝宝设计了一个简单的辅助方法
What I did was, I created a simple helper method
叫滚回去（￣Ｑ￣）╯，它包含了
called GoBack that contains
所有必要的功能代码
all of the functionality necessary
将应用置于一个合法的状态
to put the application in a valid state
在我们离开搜索功能或者点击返回按钮时
after we move away from the,
就可以使用它了
the Search functionality or whenever we hit the BackButton.
所以这就是这个方法的目的
So that's the purpose of this GoBack method.
我们要抓取所有的实例
We're going to grab all the Sounds,
我们还要设置标题，将分类信息设为
we're going to set that title, that CategoryTextBlock
“All Sounds”，侧边栏MenuItemsList设为
to AllSounds, we're going to set the MenuItemsListView
未选择的状态
to no selection,
返回键（BackButton）设置为收缩的
and then we'll set the BackButton.Visibility to Collapsed.
我要去调用它
Then I'm going to call that,
每当我点击返回键时
whenever you click the BackButton,
或者在搜索建议栏更改文字时
or whenever the text changes in the SearchAutoSuggestBox.
当你完全清空文字
So, if you clear it out completely,
或者输入了“x”时
or if you hit the little X in that AutoSuggestBox.
我们就要首先检查搜索建议栏
We're going to, first of all, check and see if
是否为空
that AutoSuggestBox is empty.
如果是的话就调用方法让它滚回去
And if it is, then we'll call GoBack
然后我们在继续
and then we'll continue on.
愚蠢的人类，见识到本宝宝的智慧了吧
So that's how I resolve that issue
莎碧问题不堪一击
that we left off with in the previous lesson.
本宝宝带领你们继续前进
Okay, so the next thing we want to do
这次来谈谈部署的问题
is talk about deployment for a little bit,
看看我们的应用是如何
and how your applications will actually be deployed
部署在终端用户电脑上的
on the end-user computer.
作为一个开发者，日常开发中
So as a developer, you don't write
你无需再为你构建的应用
any installers in your routines to install or uninstall
去写一个安装器来安装或者卸载
your Windows runtime app, the app that you're building.
相反，你打包你的程序然后提交到商店里
Instead, you package your app and you submit it
就像我们下节课要做的那样
to the Store, like we'll do in the next lesson.
用户到商店里获取你的应用
So, users will acquire your app from the Store
获取到一个我们称之为“App Package”的东西
as what's called an "App Package."
操作系统根据你在包里面提供的信息
The operating system uses information that you supply
去安装这个应用
in an app package to install the app
并且在你确认从你的设备上卸载应用时
and ensure that all traces of the app are gone
保证你应用所有的痕迹都被清理掉
from the device whenever they choose to uninstall that app.
所以这里有一个叫做 ↓ ↓ ↓ ↓ ↓  的文件
So, there's a file called the Package.appxmaninfest file,
如你所见，在方案视图中
as you can see I have it highlighted here
高亮显示的
in the Solution Explorer.
我把它调出来好让你们看到
Here let me get it up for you so you can see it.
如果我双击它你们可以看到
Alright, and if I double click it you'll see that there's
一个漂亮的设计器，但这个文件实际是
a beautiful designer, but actually what this file is,
一个XML文件,它仅仅是有一个漂亮的VS 界面
is just XML, it just has a nice Visual Studio interface
这样你就不用直接和XMl打交道了
on top of it so you don't have to deal directly with the XML.
但是本质上 ↓↓↓↓ 文件是
But essentially that Package.AppXManifest file
一个包含系统所需
is just a document that contains the information
部署信息的文档
that the system needs to deploy,
它用来展示或者升级windows应用
to display, or update a Windows app.
这些信息包含的比如像
So this information that it contains
像包的标识
will include things like the identity of the Package,
对一些动态链接库的依赖
any dependencies that it has on other DLL's
一些资源文件，和一些功能
or other resources, any capabilities,
一些申请了应用才能运行的功能
capabilities that it requires in order to run.
比如我需要GPS功能
So, I need GPS to run.
我需要使用文件系统才能运行
I need to access the file system to run.
一些视觉元素我们将在这节课演示
Any visual elements, like we're going to demonstrate
而一些扩展性的东西
in this lesson and extensibility points,
我们就不会再讨论
which we're not going to talk about.
因此每一个应用包都至少包含
So every app package must include
一个 ↓ ↓ ↓ ↓ 文件
at least one Package.AppXManifest file.
每一个包清单都作为整个包签名的一部分
So, the package manifest is digitally signed
被电子签名过
as a part of signing the app package.
在它签名之后，在无效化签名信息之前After it's been signed, then you can't modify the manifest
就不可以去修改清单文件了
without invalidating the package signature.
这就保证了相当的安全性
So there's a certain amount of security then
确保终端用户获得的是
for the end user to ensure that they're getting
你发布的应用，而不是
the application that you built
在你安装前被
and that somebody didn't hack in
别人入侵过并且
and make some changes to it
做了一些坏坏的事后坏东西
before it gets installed in their computer.
在包被安装之后
So after the package has been installed
包的清单文件就会出现在
and the package manifest file appears
你安装应用的目录下
in the directory for the install package.
这你可以看到有一排
Okay so, as you can see, there are
标签在设计器上方
a number of tabs in this designer.
他们作为一个整体，都和应用相关
Things that are related to the Application as a whole,
这个视觉资源（官译可见资产）是我们
any 'Visual Assets', that's where we're going to spend
一个重头戏
the majority of our time,
"功能"当我要说
'Capabilities', here's where I say,
我需要网络，我需要麦克风
"hey, I need the internet, I need the microphone,
我需要打电话
"I need to make a phone call."
这是我应用需要的部分
That's what my app needs.
一些声明
Any 'Declarations'
当我作为一个服务提供给我的设备或者系统
These are things that I intend to change or provide  !!不确定
我就要改变或者提供这些声明
as a service to the device or the system I'm running on.  !!不确定
内容链接，老实说我也不了解
'Content URIs', I'm not all that familiar with honestly,
但是”打包“这一部分很重要
but the 'Packaging' is important
从Windows商店来看
from a Window's Store perspective,
基本没有什么需要改变的
nothing that we really need to change,
除非我们更新一下我们应用的版本号
unless we update the version number of our application
显然，这要改一下发布者
and obviously, we'll want to change who the publisher is.
这我就直接改了
I'll go ahead and change that right now.
好，让我们直接跳到”应用“标签
So, let's go over to 'Application'.
我想我唯一想要改的是
I think the only change I want to make is
它是怎么在商店里面显示的
how it's actually displayed in the Store.
然后我还要修改一下描述
And then, I might change the description as well.
播放声音
'Plays fun sounds
用来愉♂悦和调♀戏小伙伴萌
'to amuse and amaze friends.'
也许我们需要给更好的表述
Alright, probably need a better description than that,
但这应该足够了
but that should suffice.
支持的旋转
The 'Supported rotations',
我们还没测试一下
we haven't really tested it a lot,
但我们直接选择所有
but I'm going to go ahead and select
旋转方向，基于我们所编写的方式
all of the rotations since we've programmed it
应当能够处理这些问题
in such a way that it should be able to handle it,
理想地来说，在我们勾选功能离开之前
but ideally, we would test this a little bit more
我们应当测试一下
before we just went off and made those selections.
动态磁贴我们先不动
We're not going to do any Tile Updates.
稍后我们再讨论这个话题
We'll talk about those in just a moment.
这里我要花一点时间
But we are going to do is spend time
讲一下视觉资源（可见资产）
talking about 'Visual Assets'.
让我先给应用
So, let me go ahead and
添加一个简短的名字 ：UWP SoundBoard.
add in the short name of the application: UWP SoundBoard.
以及在不同logo尺寸下
And where I want to show that name,
显示应用的名字
which versions of the logo, alright.
少年，想法不错
And it's going to say, hey that's great,
但你没有那么大Size的Logo
but you don't have a 310x310 logo.
我们分分钟搞定他
We'll fix that in just a moment.
在没走远之前
Now before we get too far into this,
宝宝有话要说，首先
let me talk about, first of all,
让你看一个你用得着的页面
let me show you a good page that you need to take a look at.
It's bit.do/tiles-badges
如你所见，屏幕上显示的是
and so, you can see here, on the the screen right now,
一个关于用户体验的文档
this is a documentation from the user experience.
这些指导准则从多方面讲诉
Guidelines that talks about the various ways
这些视觉资源如何使用在设备上
that visual assets will be used on the device
比如在开始界面和开始菜单上
on the start screen or on the start menu.
我不准备花时间在这上面
And, I'm not going to take the time to cover all of these.
这的确是一个很长的列表
There's actually quite a long list,
从这里着手我稍稍讲一些定义
but let me give you a few definitions to begin with here.
一个磁贴就是这个不幸
A tile is anything, and unfortunately,
被贴在屏幕左手边
it's going to be off to the left
的小东西
hand side of the screen here,
你可以看到,,这是一个磁贴
but you can see, like, this is a tile,
电源电视磁贴,Groove 音乐磁贴
this Movies & TV tile, this Groove Music tile,
新闻磁贴,就是这些
this News Tile, okay.
他们方向不同，并且他们的表现方式也不大相同
Different orientations and what they do
比如你可以看到,
are a little bit differently, because you can see
新闻这个磁贴上有一张图片
that there are some, the News Items has a photograph,
但广而言之，他们最终都是
but ultimately, those are all tiles,
一些磁贴而已
in a very general sense.
这里有个东西叫“动态磁贴”
Now, there is something called a 'Live tile',
他们是被称作Metro或者Modern用户界面
which is, that which typifies that what they called
的典型代表
Metro or Modern User Interface,
在他们所在的位置，会有信息快速翻动
where there are, there's information that gets flipped.
一些新的信息或者不同的信息
New information, different information,
如果你装了一个新应用
so if you have a news application,
它可能顺序展示三四个崭新的画面
you might show three or four news stories
或者给一些更新的内容
in sequence or give some sort of an update.
但这些只是给特定类型的动态磁贴
But this, too, is kind of a general heading for
的通用定义而已
specific types of live tiles.
比如还有所谓的磁贴通知
For example, there are 'Tile notifications'.
像常见的，如果你用过一个邮件应用
And these are usually, like, if you see a mail program,
你有六个新的邮件，好
you have six new emails, okay.
在磁贴的底部通常有一个小的标志，告诉你
There's usually a little badge at the bottom with a number that tells you how many
你有多少东西新更新了，需要你注意一下
items are new and updated and require your attention.
这有一个称为标记的东西
Then are things called badges,
它会出现，事实上他表示
and that will show, actually badges
你的事物的数量
show you the number of items.
磁贴通知是针对每一个用户
Tile notifications are pieces of information
的一系列的消息
that are specific on a per user basis.
比如我正在玩一个电子游戏
So if I'm playing a video game,
我的飞船将在3小时后到达一个星球
and my ship actually lands at a planet three hours later,
我把它发送后，之后我就会收到
after I sent it there, then I might get
一个磁贴通知，它告诉我
a notification, a tile notification that says,
"嘿，是时候回来玩游戏啦“
"Hey, it's time to come back and play now,
'又有你可以采取的动作啦”
"there's action that you can take."
之后是标记，就像我们提到过的
Then there's 'Badges', like we talked about,
六条信息，需要你注意一下
number of six messages that need your attention.
还有一个叫"预览样式"
And then there's a 'Peek template',
从磁贴上你可以看到内容的一部分
where you can actually see portions of the content,
像使用一张照片
like, maybe a photo that will be utilized
如果你用磁贴启动应用
if you were to then launch the application from that tile,
使用预览样式，你可以
so you get to peek at the content inside of that tile,
从中一览部分内容
using a peek template.
再次，你可以看一眼这些准则
And, again, you can take a look at these guidelines,
其中可能和我们最相关的是
probably the biggest one that is pertinent to us,
在我们的应用中，我应当只使用for our application is that we should only use
中小型的磁贴
a small and medium tile.
你可以看到，这里有很多尺寸的磁贴
So there are different size tiles, as you can see here,
不同大小不同形状
there are different size and shape tiles,
一个准则就是不能使用大的磁贴
and one of the guidelines is you shouldn't use a large tile,
如果你既没有使用通知
if you're not using tile notifications
也没有使用标记
and if you're not using badges,
那你应该使用中小型的磁贴
so we should only use small and medium,
而不是大号的
not the larger ones, okay.
你会注意到，默认情况下
Now you'll notice that by default,
已经有一些资源已经准备好了
there are a number of assets that are already,
可以说是为你预定义好了
kind of, predefined for you.
比如，这个方形150*150的logo
For example, this square 150x150 logo.
你可以看到
You can see that,
嗯。。我们首先到所有图片资源下
that by, well first of all, let me go to All Image Assets,
它会给我们长长的列表
then that'll give us a longer list,
这里通常你能做的仅仅是去
that usually what you can do is just
选择一个推荐的尺寸
choose one of the recommended sizes
或者两个，其他的尺寸
or two of the recommended sizes and the other scales
会自动为你生成
will be automatically generated for you.
这我就先放着
Now what I've gone off and done,
因为我也不完全确定
because I wasn't really entirely sure
我需要提供什么
what I needed to provide.
我停一下，告诉我的图形设计器
I went off and told my graphic designer to,
嘿，给朕照着他们的要求
"Hey, give me my little logo here
每一个尺寸的都给呈一份
in all these different variety of sizes that they ask for."
然后朕再回过头来
And then, I might come back and then
把那些狗屁不通的都斩了
remove the ones that don't make a whole lot of sense.
我这里要稍微花一点时间调试一下
So, I'm going to take some time here and change out,
比如这个 方块71*71的logo
like for example, the square 71x71 logo.
我要到这个省略号这里
I might go here to the little ellipses
去选择一个图片放进这个槽里
to actually select an image file to copy in this slot.
我要进入资源的文件夹
I'm going to go into the Assets folder,
进入PackageAppXManifest 文件夹中
into my PackageAppXManifest folder,
然后找一下71*71的图像
and I'm looking for the 71x71 image, like so.
现在它说它不喜欢我的命名方式
Now it says that it doesn't like my naming convention
名称中要提供尺寸信息
and that it has to provide some scaling
像是要在71*71和扩展名中夹一层
information, kind of, sandwiched between the 71x71
你想要处理吗？
and the .png, do you want to proceed?
Absolutely, go right ahead.
Okay and, so you can see that it puts it there now.
I can also add a background color.
I think we'll just add a background color of,
well, in the case of the tiles,
we want the background color to be transparent
because we want to use whatever the system colors are,
but for the splash screen, let's use red.
Let's see if it'll accept that.
We'll come back to that in a little bit.
All right, so let's go ahead and continue on here.
I'll choose a 300x300.
Okay so, I think that's pretty much everything
that I want to change about this.
So let's close this now and what I want to do
before we leave this topic,
is actually right-click the Package.AppXManifest file
and just say, Open With,
and I'm just going to open with the Text Editor,
or maybe just the XML Text Editor and click OK.
And then you can see all of the settings that we made
in that designer and you can see how they're manifest here
in the XML, alright?
And so, that's really all that I wanted to do.
Let me do this, though.
Let me save this and now let me run it.
I'd like to see if the splash screen pops up.
All right, and you saw the splash screen briefly there.
That's really cool.
Looks like I'm going to need to also add a little space there.
I forgot about, let me do that real quick
before we conclude this video.
And if you recall, I said this several times
how I wanted to put a Margin around this thing,
maybe: "0,5,10,0".
Now let's run it one more time.
There's our cool splash screen,
and that looks pretty nice, okay.
Alright, so ideally we would test this a little bit more,
maybe run it on some friends' computers,
other devices, test with the various mobile emulators
that are available.
But I'm going to wing it
and I'm actually going to try and submit this
in the next video to the Store, so we'll see you there.
Thanks.